<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Brainu</string>
    <string name="folder_name">.brainu/upload</string>
    <string name="url">https://aziziitblab.co.in/brainu/upload.php</string>
    <string name="stop_recording">Stop Recording</string>
    <string name="start_recording">Start Recording</string>
    <string name="play_audio">Play Audio</string>
    <string name="stop_audio">Stop Audio</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_start">Click hear to Start</string>
    <string name="press_here">Click here to Start recording</string>

    <string name="vc_starting_question">Brainu is in a dense forest to identify different varieties of leaves and flowers. Help Brainu Identify the different consonants too. Listen to the options given and choose the correct one.</string>
    <string name="vowels_question">The Vowels and Consonants are shown. Listen to the options that are played one by one. Tap on them Individually to play again. To answer, double tap the option till it turns green then tap the confirm button.</string>

    <string name="after_finish">\nCongratulations\n You Did it !!!\n</string>
    <string name="after_finish_btn">Click here for next</string>
    <string name="word_reading_question">Brainu is at the beach. He is holding a board that will show a few words. Help him read them out by recording your answer. The word will appear only when you tap.</string>
    <string name="all_the_best">\nAll The Best\n</string>
    <string name="paragraph_reading_question">Brainu wants to listen to a story but he is not able to read. But you can help him! Please read out the short story from his story book. It will appear after you tap Start.</string>
    <string name="paragraph_reading_0">Ants are found everywhere in the world. They make their home in buildings, gardens etc. They live in anthills. Ants are very hardworking insects. Throughout the summers they collect food for the winter season. Whenever they find a sweet lying on the floor they stick to the sweet and carry it to their home.</string>
    <string name="paragraph_reading_1">Today is Holi the festival of colours. Ranis brother Ravi and their parents have got ready with white clothes and have bought colourful eco friendly packets of colours. They include pink gulal, red vermilion, yellow turmeric and green leaf powder colour. They are ready to play dry holi with minimum wastage of water and lots of happiness, unity, sweets and treats.</string>
    <string name="paragraph_reading_2">There is a candy shop in Hoshiyaarpur. Ramu Bhaiyya is the owner of the shop and sells all types of candies, sweet and sour treats, chocolates and toffees. He has colourful candies, jelly candies and digestive confectioneries. He loves to sell these as children from all over the town come to his shop to buy these. He is a very kind man and often gives free sweets.</string>
    <string name="paragraph_reading_3">once upon a time. The three bulls were very good friends among themselves. They used to go to graze grass together. A lion had been following them all for many days, but he knew that as long as these three are united, he cannot spoil them. The lion did the trick to separate the three from each other. He started blowing rumors about Ballo. After hearing the rumors, misunderstanding arose between them. Gradually they started burning with each other. Eventually one day they got into a fight and they started living separately. This was a great opportunity for the lion. He took full advantage of it and killed all three one by one and ate.\nlearning - There is power in unity.</string>
    <string name="paragraph_reading_4"></string>
    <string name="paragraph_reading_5"></string>
    <string name="spoonerism_question">To help Brainu perform the Spoonerism Step, exchange the first letters of the pair of words and tell Brainu what the new pair is! Tap on the words to listen. Tap START to begin</string>
    <string name="first_word">1st Word</string>
    <string name="second_word">2nd Word</string>
    <string name="syllable_deletion_question">ब्रेनू को यह बताने में मदद करें कि दिए गए शब्द से विशिष्ट ध्वनि निकालने के बाद शब्द क्या होगा।  आवाज सुनने के लिए ध्वनि और शब्द आइकन पर टैप करें।</string>
    <string name="tifa">Tap it for audio</string>
    <string name="from_the"> from the</string>
    <string name="remove_from">Remove the</string>
    <string name="word"> Word </string>
    <string name="sound"> Sound </string>
    <string name="dictation_consonent_1">Brainu is in a quiet and peaceful forest, \n to listen to the sounds of birds and nature. Words will be dictated. \nHelp Brain by typing the word that is dictated!</string>
    <string name="answer_here">Write Answer here...</string>
    <string name="now_write_answer">\nnow Write your Answer\n</string>
    <string name="dictation_consonent_write">Click on write and write the word on the white board</string>
	<string name="start_write">Write</string>
	<string name="clean">Clear</string>

    <string name="phoneme_substitution_question">Help Brainu by telling him what new word will be formed when sound 1 is substituted with sound 2 in the given word. \nTap on sound 1, sound 2, and word icons on the board for audio.</string>
    <string name="phoneme_deletion_question">Help Brainu by telling him what the remaining word would be, after you remove the specific sound from the given word. Tap on sound and  word icons one the board to listen to the audio.</string>
    <string name="ran_question_1">Help Brainu to understand what is pinned on the board. \nCertain items will appear on the notes. Say them out loud from left to right as fast as you can.</string>
    <string name="ran_iteration_1">Your question is - Letters\nAll The Best !!!</string>
    <string name="ran_iteration_2">Your question is - Objects\nAll The Best !!!</string>
    <string name="ran_iteration_3">Your question is - Objects\nAll The Best !!!</string>
    <string name="ran_iteration_4">Your question is - Colors\nAll The Best !!!</string>

    <string name="substitute">substitute</string>
    <string name="with">with</string>
    <string name="in">in</string>
    <string name="sound1">sound 1</string>
    <string name="sound2">sound 2</string>

    <string name="email_id">Email Id</string>
    <string name="user_name">user name</string>
    <string name="password"></string>
    <string name="age">Age</string>
    <string name="laguage">Language</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="downloadStarted">Downloading...</string>
    <string name="downloadCompleted">Processing...</string>
    <string name="downloadFailed">Download Failed !!!</string>
    <string name="downloadAgain">Try Again !!!</string>
    <string name="checkInternet">Check Your Internet Connection !!!</string>
    <string name="searching">Searching...</string>
    <string name="oops">Ooops !!!</string>
    <string name="no_internet">No Internet Found ! Check Your Connection</string>

    <string name="v_c_reading">Letter</string>
    <string name="dictation">Listen</string>
    <string name="ran">Identify</string>
    <string name="word_reading">Word</string>
    <string name="spoonerism">Swapping</string>
    <string name="paragraph">Story</string>
    <string name="phoneme_1">Word game 1</string>
    <string name="phoneme_2">Word game 2</string>
    <string name="phoneme_3">Word game 3</string>
    <string name="phoneme_4">Word game 4</string>

    <string name="resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="select_your_games">Select your games</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="you_win">You Won !!!</string>
    <string name="you_did_it">You did it !!!</string>
    <string name="unlock_next">Unlock next</string>
    <string name="unlocking">Unlocking...</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <string name="restart">Restart</string>
    <string name="read_text">Read Text</string>
    <string name="read_question">Read Question</string>
    <string name="select_correct_one">Select correct one</string>
    <string name="double_click_to_select">Double click to select</string>
    <string name="click_to_submit">Click here to submit</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_record">Click here to record</string>
    <string name="identify_and_speak">Identify and speak</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_stop">Click here to stop</string>
    <string name="read_text_loudly">Read text loudly</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_play">Click here to play</string>
    <string name="click_to_start_and_listen_audio_carefully">Click to start and listen audio carefully</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_write">Click here to write</string>
    <string name="write_here">Write here</string>
    <string name="click_here_to_listen">Click here to listen</string>
    <string name="rotate">Rotate</string>
    <string name="games">Games</string>

</resources>
